<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CityLink on Brisbane CBD Bicycle User Group (BUG)</title>
    <link>https://brisbanecbdbug.org/tags/citylink/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CityLink on Brisbane CBD Bicycle User Group (BUG)</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://brisbanecbdbug.org/tags/citylink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Misuse of Bus Lanes / Jump Zones</title>
      <link>https://brisbanecbdbug.org/our-letters/letter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://brisbanecbdbug.org/our-letters/letter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;misuse-of-bus-lanes--jump-zones&#34;&gt;Misuse of bus lanes / jump zones&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-we-are-concerned&#34;&gt;Why we are concerned?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Brisbane Central Business District Bicycle User Group (CBD BUG) is concerned about the ongoing misuse of bus lanes and jump zones by private motorists, which significantly diminishes the benefits of these spaces for cyclists and public transport users. Despite the legal allowance for cyclists to use bus lanes, many drivers ignore this and obstruct the lanes, undermining their intended purpose. Although occasional police enforcement is carried out, it is insufficient to deter this widespread issue due to limited resources. The group is requesting the installation of camera surveillance technology to automatically detect and penalize motorists who violate the rules, particularly in the inner city.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Cycle with your Dog!</title>
      <link>https://brisbanecbdbug.org/blog/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://brisbanecbdbug.org/blog/post-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;how-to-cycle-with-your-dog-and-the-benefits-of-cycling-together&#34;&gt;How to Cycle with Your Dog and the Benefits of Cycling Together&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cycling with your dog can be a fun and rewarding experience, offering both of you exercise, fresh air, and bonding time. However, ensuring safety and comfort for both you and your furry companion is key. In this article, we’ll cover how to cycle with your dog safely and the many benefits of doing so.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
